let questions17 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "affection",
      answer: "C. Zuneigung",
      options: [
        "A. Liebe",
        "B. Gefühl",
        "C. Zuneigung",
        "D. Sympathie"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "agency",
      answer: "A. Agentur",
      options: [
        "A. Agentur",
        "B. Büro",
        "C. Vertretung",
        "D. Geschäft"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "ash",
      answer: "D. Asche",
      options: [
        "A. Staub",
        "B. Ruß",
        "C. Pulver",
        "D. Asche"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "to confine",
      answer: "B. einschließen",
      options: [
        "A. begrenzen",
        "B. einschließen",
        "C. einsperren",
        "D. beschränken"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "to dismiss",
      answer: "C. ablehnen",
      options: [
        "A. verwerfen",
        "B. ignorieren",
        "C. ablehnen",
        "D. abweisen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "to erupt",
      answer: "A. ausbrechen",
      options: [
        "A. ausbrechen",
        "B. explodieren",
        "C. platzen",
        "D. bersten"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "fate",
      answer: "D. Schicksal",
      options: [
        "A. Los",
        "B. Bestimmung",
        "C. Geschick",
        "D. Schicksal"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "lava",
      answer: "B. Lava",
      options: [
        "A. Magma",
        "B. Lava",
        "C. Gestein",
        "D. Masse"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "miserable",
      answer: "C. elend",
      options: [
        "A. traurig",
        "B. unglücklich",
        "C. elend",
        "D. erbärmlich"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to navigate",
      answer: "A. steuern",
      options: [
        "A. steuern",
        "B. lenken",
        "C. leiten",
        "D. führen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "to originate",
      answer: "D. entstehen",
      options: [
        "A. beginnen",
        "B. stammen",
        "C. kommen",
        "D. entstehen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "remainder",
      answer: "B. Rest",
      options: [
        "A. Überbleibsel",
        "B. Rest",
        "C. Restbestand",
        "D. Rückstand"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "to retrieve",
      answer: "C. zurückholen",
      options: [
        "A. finden",
        "B. bergen",
        "C. zurückholen",
        "D. holen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "shallow",
      answer: "A. flach",
      options: [
        "A. flach",
        "B. seicht",
        "C. untief",
        "D. niedrig"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "slope",
      answer: "D. Hang",
      options: [
        "A. Abhang",
        "B. Böschung",
        "C. Neigung",
        "D. Hang"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to span",
      answer: "B. überspannen",
      options: [
        "A. dauern",
        "B. überspannen",
        "C. erstrecken",
        "D. reichen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "superstition",
      answer: "C. Aberglaube",
      options: [
        "A. Glaube",
        "B. Mythos",
        "C. Aberglaube",
        "D. Vorstellung"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "sympathy",
      answer: "A. Mitgefühl",
      options: [
        "A. Mitgefühl",
        "B. Mitleid",
        "C. Anteilnahme",
        "D. Sympathie"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "to vibrate",
      answer: "D. vibrieren",
      options: [
        "A. zittern",
        "B. beben",
        "C. schwingen",
        "D. vibrieren"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "to wander",
      answer: "B. umherwandern",
      options: [
        "A. spazieren",
        "B. umherwandern",
        "C. schlendern",
        "D. streifen"
      ]
    }
];

export default questions17;